<!-- Copyright (C) 2016 The Android Open Source Project

     Licensed under the Apache License, Version 2.0 (the "License");
     you may not use this file except in compliance with the License.
     You may obtain a copy of the License at

          http://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0

     Unless required by applicable law or agreed to in writing, software
     distributed under the License is distributed on an "AS IS" BASIS,
     WITHOUT WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF ANY KIND, either express or implied.
     See the License for the specific language governing permissions and
     limitations under the License.
-->
<resources>
    <!-- Title for the application. [CHAR LIMIT=12] -->
    <string name="app_name">Tour Guide</string>


    <string name="category_monuments">Monuments</string>


    <string name="category_malls">Malls</string>


    <string name="category_hotels">Hotels</string>


    <string name="category_food">Food</string>

    <string name="category_songs">Music</string>
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">hello frennns</string>


    <string-array name="food_dishes">
        <item>Chicken Karahi</item>
        <item>Seekh Kabab</item>
        <item>Biryani</item>
        <item>Sweet Punjabi Lassi</item>
        <item>Halwa Poori</item>
        <item>Kheer</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="hotel_names">
        <item>Pearl Continental</item>
        <item>Avari Hotel</item>
        <item>Hospitality Inn</item>
        <item>Faletti Hotel</item>
        <item>The Nishat Hotel</item>
        <item>Kheer</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="monument_names">
        <item>Badshahi Mosque</item>
        <item>Lahore Fort</item>
        <item>Minar-e-Pakistan</item>
        <item>Wazir Khan Mosque</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="mall_names">
        <item>Emporium Mall</item>
        <item>Mall of Lahore</item>
        <item>Fortress Square</item>
        <item>Anarkali Bazar</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="song_names">
        <item>Afreen</item>
        <item>Jazba Junoon</item>
        <item>Sammi Meri Waar</item>
    </string-array>
    <string name="badshahi_mosque">\n\nThe Badshahi Mosque is a Mughal era masjid in Lahore, capital of the Pakistani
        province of Punjab, Pakistan. The mosque is located west of Lahore Fort along the outskirts of the Walled City
        of Lahore, and is widely considered to be one of the most iconic landmarks in the world. Badshahi Mosque was
        commissioned by Emperor Aurangzeb in 1671, with construction of the mosque lasting for two years until 1673.
        The mosque is an important example of Mughal architecture, with an exterior that is decorated with carved red
        sandstone with marble inlay. It remains the largest and most recent of the grand imperial mosques of the
        Mughal-era, and is the second-largest mosque in Pakistan.\n\n</string>
    <string name="lahore_fort">\n\nThe Lahore Fort, is a citadel in the city of Lahore,Punjab, Pakistan. The fortress
        is located at the northern end of walled city Lahore, and spreads over an area greater than 20 hectares.
        It contains 21 notable monuments, some of which date to the era of Emperor Akbar. The Lahore Fort is notable
        for having been almost entirely rebuilt in the 17th century, when the Mughal Empire was at the height of
        its splendour and opulence. Though the site of the Lahore Fort has been inhabited for millennia,
        the first record of a fortified structure at the site was in regard to an 11th-century mud-brick fort.
        The foundations of the modern Lahore Fort date to 1566 during the reign of Emperor Akbar, who bestowed the
        fort with a syncretic architectural style that featured both Islamic and Hindu motifs.
        Additions from the Shah Jahan period are characterized by luxurious marble with inlaid Persian floral designs,
        while the forts grand and iconic Alamgiri Gate was constructed by the last of the great Mughal Emperors,
        Aurangzeb, and faces the renowned Badshahi Mosque.\n\n\</string>
    <string name="minar_e_pakistan">\n\nMinar-e-Pakistan is a national monument located in Lahore, Pakistan.
        The tower was built between 1960 and 1968 on the site where the All-India Muslim League passed the
        Lahore Resolution on 23 March 1940 - the first official call for a separate and independent homeland for the
        Muslims of British India, as espoused by the two-nation theory. The resolution eventually helped lead to the
        emergence of an independent Pakistani state in 1947.\n\n</string>
    <string name="wazir_khan_mosque">\n\nConsidered to be the most ornately decorated Mughal-era mosque, Wazir Khan
        Mosque is renowned for its intricate faience tile work known as kashi-kari, as well as its interior surfaces
        that are almost entirely embellished with elaborate Mughal-era frescoes. </string>
    <string name="emporium_mall">\n\nCONTACT INFO\n\tAdjacent to Lahore \n\tInternational Expo Centre,
        \n\tAbdul Haque Rd\n\tJohar Town, Lahore, Pakistan\n\t+92 42 3259 2000
        \n\tinfo@nishatemporium.com\n\tnishatemporium.com\n\n
    </string>
    <string name="mall_of_lahore">\n\nPark Lane Tower, \n172 Tufail Road, Lahore Cantt.\nTel: +92 42 111 111 980
        \nFax: +92 42 662 2449\n\n</string>
    <string name="fortress_square">\n Fortress Square Lahore\n\tFood court,\n\tState of the art cinema,Cinepax.
        \n\t100+ Shopping Brands\n\tValet parking\n\n</string>
    <string name="anarkali_bazar">\n\nAnarkali remains one of the oldest surviving markets in South Asia, dating back at
        least 200 years and derives its name from the nearby mausoleum thought to be that of a courtesan girl named
        Anārkalī, who was chased out of town by order of the Mughal Emperor Akbar for having a love affair with his
        son, Prince Salīm, who would later become Emperor Jahāngīr. Anarkali mainly sells textiles, garments,
        jewellery, and many other items.\n\n</string>
    <string name="karahi">\n\nChicken karahi, also known as gosht karahi, and kadai chicken, is a dish from the
        Indian subcontinent noted for its spicy taste; it is notable in Pakistani and North Indian cuisine.
        The Pakistani version does not have capsicum or onions whereas the North Indian version uses capsicum.
        The dish is prepared in a karahi.\n\n</string>
    <string name="kabab">\n\nSeekh kebab is a type of kebab, originating from the Indian subcontinent, made with Indian
        spices mixed with minced or ground meat, formed into cylinders on skewers and grilled. It is typically 
        cooked on a mangal or barbecue, or in a tandoor.\n\n</string>
    <string name="biryani">\n\nBiryani, is a mixed rice dish that originates from the Muslims of the Indian subcontinent.
        This dish is especially popular throughout the Indian subcontinent, as well as among the diaspora from the 
        region. It is also prepared in other regions such as Iraqi Kurdistan. It is made with Indian spices, rice, meat
        (chicken, goat, beef, prawn, or fish), vegetables or eggs.\n\n</string>
    <string name="lassi">\n\nLassi is a blend of yogurt, water, spices and sometimes fruit. Traditional lassi
        (a.k.a., "sweet lassi", or simply "lassi") is a sweet savoury drink, sometimes flavoured with ground and
        roasted cumin. Salty lassi, however, contains salt and other spices, instead of sugar, and is similar to
        doogh.\n\n</string>
    <string name="poori">\n\nPuri (also spelled Poori) is an unleavened deep-fried bread, originating from South Asia.
        It is eaten for breakfast or as a snack or light meal. It is usually served with a savory curry or bhaji,
        as in Puri bhaji, but may also be eaten with sweet dishes. Puris are most commonly served at breakfast.
        It is also served at special or ceremonial functions as part of ceremonial rituals along with other
        vegetarian food offered in prayer as prasadam. It is similar to Gnocco fritto fried bread from Modena,
        Italy.\n\n</string>
    <string name="kheer">\n\nKheer is a rice pudding, originating from the Indian subcontinent from the state of Punjab,
        made by boiling with milk and sugar one of the following: rice, broken wheat, tapioca, vermicelli,
        sweet corn, etc. It is flavoured with cardamom, raisins, saffron, cashews, pistachios, almonds or other
        dry fruits and nuts. It is typically served during a meal or as a dessert.
        It is also known in some regions as meetha bhaat, payasam, payasa, and phirni.\n\n</string>
    <string name="pc">\nPearl Continental Lahore\n\tShara-e-Quaid-e-Azam, Lahore.\n\tTel: 92-42-111 505 505
        \n\tFax: 92-42-3636 2698\n\tE-mail: pchl@pchotels.com\n\tWebsite: www.pchotels.com\n\t
        Facebook: www.facebook.com/PC.Lahore</string>
    <string name="nishat">\nThe Nishat Hotel\n\t9A Mian Mahmud Kasuri Road, Gulberg III, Lahore
        \n\tTel: +92-042-111-000-777\n\tEmail: info@nishathotel.com</string>
    <string name="flattei">Contact Info\n\t24 – Egerton Road,\nLahore 54000.\n\tPakistan\nUAN # 042-111-444-333
\n\tTel: 92 42 36363946 - 51\n\tFax # 92 42 36366818\n\tEmail: info@falettishotel.com\n\tcomplaints@falettishotel.com</string>
<string name="avari">\nAvari Lahore\n\t87Shahrah-e-Quaid-e-Azam\n\tLahore 54000\n\tPakistan\n\tTel: (92-42) 3-6366366
\n\tUAN: 111 AVARIS (111 282 747)\n\tToll-Free: 0800-88888\n\tFax: (92-42) 3-6365367\n\tEmail: lahore@avari.com</string>
    <string name="hos">\nHospitality Inn Lahore\n\tAddress :  25 Egerton Road, Lahore.\n\tPhone	: +92-42-36310077\n\tFax:+92-42-36314514</string>
</resources>